>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 现在我的论点是即使你能做到这两者
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Now my argument is that
even though you could do both of these
因此，您应该只在 for 循环上使用 let 来执行该变量。
with let, you should only do
the variable on the for loop with let.
如果您有一个属于整个函数作用域的变量，
If you have a variable that belongs
to the entire scope of the function,
向您的读者发出信号的正确语法方法是
the correct syntactic way to signal
that to your reader is not to
在功能作用域的顶级使用 let ，但是
use a let at the top level
of your function scope, but
用一个 var cuz 来做这件事 24 年的事
to use a var cuz that the thing
it's always done for 24 years.
>> Kyle Simpson: 如果您要将 var 替换为 let，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: If you were to
replace the var online with a let,
即使在这个特殊的例子中，它仍会运作正常。
even though in this particular example
it would still functionally work.
我的论点是它会去除一些重要的语义
My argument is that it would remove
a small amount of important semantic
读者的信息，因为读者不知道，
information from the reader,
because the reader would then not know,
你的意图是什么
well what is your intent?
你打算让我到处使用还是你的意图
Is your intent for me to use it
everywhere or is your intent for
我只能在此发挥作用吗
me to only use here at
the very top of the function?
我也不知道因为我们要用一个
I don't really know,
because lets are supposed to signal a very
变量的本地化使用，理想情况下仅在几行代码中使用。
localized usage of a variable, ideally
within only a couple of lines of code.
如果你想在整个函数中使用变量
And if you're intent is to use
the variable across the whole function,
允许关键字起作用，但它不是正确的工具。
the let keyword might work,
but it's not the right tool.
这不是工具的正确用法。
It's not the right usage of the tool.
你以前听过那个 adage 如果你要把它放进去或者你会放
You've heard that adage before, if you are
gonna put a screw in or you're gonna put
你应该选择正确的工具和锤子
a nail in, you should choose the right
tool, hammer versus, all right.
但我要把类比的范围扩大到只有你选择正确的工具
But I'm gonna extend that analogy, cuz not
only should you choose the right tool,
如果我有钉子我就有个锤子
if I had a nail and I had a hammer,
I've done some home repair and
我可以合理地把锤子放在墙上，把钉子钉在墙上，好的。
I could probably reasonably put a hammer
into a wall, put a nail into a wall, okay.
但如果我有同样的工具和同样的钉子
But what would happen if I had the same
tool and the same nail and to put
墙上的钉子，我把锤子放进嘴里，我就做了， [SOUND]。
the nail in the wall, I put the hammer
in my mouth and I just did, [SOUND].
我有正确的工具，但我用的是错误的工具。
I have the right tool for the right job
but I'm using the tool the wrong way.
拥有正确的工具是不够的
It's not enough to have the right tool,
你得用正确的工具
you need to use the right
tool the right way.
所以尽管我们也许是个能工作的工具
So even though let might
be a tool that would work,
它不是用正确的方式使用的
it's not being used in the correct way.
>> Kyle Simpson: 此处的 var 关键字是更合适的工具来表示我有
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: The var keyword here is
a more appropriate tool to say I have
应该使用的变量。
a variable that should be used across.
这是一个思想实验，想象一个人要设计
Here's a thought experiment,
imagine somebody were to design
仅允许您使用的编程语言
a programming language
that only allowed you to
在函数的第一行上访问函数的任何参数。
access any parameters to a function on
the very first line of the function.
在第一条线之外，你无法访问这些参数。
And beyond the first line you
couldn't access the parameters.
你有多少人会觉得这会是一种有趣的语言
How many of you would find
that to be a fun language
你有多少人能用语言来让人讨厌的限制
versus how many of you would find that to
be an annoying restriction in a language?
我觉得原因，这就是我要做的事，是自然的
I think the reason, and this is what
I'm getting at, is it is natural
在代码的设计中有些东西不是块的
within the design of code that
some things are not block scoped.
有些东西是，如果你有自然阻塞的东西，
Some things are, and if you have
something that is naturally block scoped,
请允许使用。
please use let.
我什么都没说让我们去阻止范围
I'm not saying anything about let,
use let to block scope,
这正是它所需要的
that's exactly what it's for.
但请不要去找那些不是自然允许的东西
But please don't go looking to make things
into lets that aren't naturally lets.
怎么了 >> 演讲者 1:
Yes?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: So
如果您使用 ESLint，我认为缺省设置是如果您使用 var，
if you use ESLint, I think the default
setting is that if you use var,
那你就会得到意想不到的消息，或者其他的方式，对吧。
then you get the unexpected let,
or the other way around, right.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 这是真的。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: That's true.
我不同意他们的意见
And I just disagree with them, and
我的规定是在我自己的 ESLint 中关闭的，好的。
I have that rule turned off
in my own ESLint, okay.
不允许您对其进行定制并改为强制实施的任何工具
Any tool that doesn't allow you to
customize it and instead enforces
它自己对你的看法，是一个不帮你的工具，就在你的路上。
its own opinion on you, is a tool that's
not helping you, it's getting in your way.
我认为这并不是真正的帮助你的方法。
And I would argue it's not really
getting in your way in a helpful way.
它在你的路上妨碍了你的交流
It's getting on your way and
preventing you from communicating.
怎么了
Yes?
>> 扬声器 2: 要查看第 2 行 ( 如果存在 var 或 let ) ，那么将
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: To review for line two,
if we have var or let, will the variable
在 - >> Kyle Simpson中以相同方式运行 : 在此特定代码中
function in the same way in the-
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: In this particular code
片段它们的行为相同。
snippet they will behave the same.
所以我现在在这张幻灯片上做的就是一个风格的观点。
So all I'm making the case right now on
this exact slide is a stylistic argument.
我要做个更重要的事来解释为什么你有时想要
I'm about to make a bigger case for
why you sometimes want var,
但现在我只为 var 做个造型论
but right now I'm only making
a stylistic argument for var.
var 的语义参数，好的。
A semantic argument for var, okay.
[ COUGH] 所以如果你有一个变量要出现在
[COUGH] So if you have a variable
that is going to show up in
一个被认为是一个街区的地方
a place that would otherwise
be considered a block and
你用一个，猜猜那个变量会怎么样 ?
you use a let,
guess what happens to that variable?
无论您是否希望，它都将连接到该块。
Whether you want it to or not,
it attaches to that block.
我经常遇到的一个例子是，如果我尝试使用一个
One of the examples that I often run
across is if I'm trying to use a let and
我把它用在 try - catch 块里面
I use it inside of a try-catch block,
我不认为它是一个街区，我不认为它是一个范围。
I don't think of try-catch as a block,
I don't think of it as a scope.
我认为它是一种捕捉例外情况的句法
I think of it as a syntactic
way to catch exceptions,
不是特别设计好的，但我们是如何捕捉到例外的。
not even a particularly well designed one,
but it is how we catch exceptions.
我当然不认为它是一个隐藏空间的地方。
I certainly don't think of it
as a place for me to hide scope.
然而，让关键词和
And yet, the let keyword and
常量关键字块作用域本身。
the const keyword block scope
themselves inside of it.
那么，如果我们从 var 中找到和替换我们的全球发现和替换，会发生什么呢 ?
So guess what would happen if we did our
global find and replace from var to let?
这个代码将会中断，因为在第 9 行上没有标识。
This code would break because there
wouldn't be an id on line nine.
Var hoists ，我们会把它弄回来的，但是
Var hoists,
we'll get it back to hoisting, but
var 将自身附加到函数作用域。
var attaches itself to the function scope.
在这种情况下，我想说，这也许不是一直存在的问题，但
And I would argue in cases like this,
which arguably are not all the time, but
在某些情况下， var 关键字更可取
in some cases,
the var keyword is preferable to the let
因为它能够在此情况下转义非预期的块。
keyword because it is able, in this case,
to escape an unintended block.
>> Kyle Simpson: 此处的替代方法是在外部声明 var
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: The alternative here
would have been to declare a var outside
就像我们之前做过的几张幻灯片一样，在两个地方给它分配。
of the try, just like we did a few slides
ago, and then assign to it in two places.
我想说的是你越添加代码的越多
And I would argue that the more
that you add lines of code to that,
另外，您将声明与任务分配分开，对于
the further you separate the declaration
from the assignment, the harder it is for
人们要理解
people to understand.
这就是我喜欢用 " var" 之类的东西来的地方之一。
So this is one of those places where I
tend to prefer using something like a var.
当我们在讨论 var 的话题时，瓦尔能做的另一件事是
While we're on the topic of var, another
thing that var can do which let can not is
您可以在作用域内多次使用 var 。
that you can use var more
than once inside of a scope.
此变量在函数作用域中使用了两次，并且
Here var is being used twice
within a function scope, and
我们也不会有任何例外
we're not gonna get any
exceptions whatsoever.
我在网上用了 6 个变量因为我想澄清
And I used the var online six
because I was trying to disambiguate
这里的 id 是从哪里来的
where id comes from.
这是我发送给读者的语意信号
This is a semantic signal that
I'm sending to the reader,
不管我们经历了什么
regardless of which path we go through,
在功能范围内肯定会有一个标识它会有一个价值
there's gonna be an id in the function
scope and it's gonna have a value.
所以我把 var 放在两个地方，我可以这样做，因为那是 var 可以做的。
So I put var in both places, and I can
do that because that's what var can do.
我不能用一个 let来
I can't do that with a let.
我不经常这样做就像我说的那样
I don't do this that often,
as again as I've said.
这不是在代码中发生的事情。
This is not something that
happens a lot in the code.
但在发生这种情况的地方我认为
But in the places that it happens,
I think that it is better that var is
具有不同功能的工具就会被允许。
a tool that has a different
capability then does let.
如果我采纳了一些完全禁止使用 var的 ESLint 规则，
And if I had adopted some ESLint rule
that completely forbid all uses of var,
在此场景中，我将受到限制。
I would be restricted in this scenario.
这里是另一个我喜欢用 var 来区分范围的地方。
Here's another place where I like to use
the var for the disambiguation of scope.
我倾向于我的功能不超过 15 或 20 行代码。
I tended to prefer my functions to be no
longer than about 15 or 20 lines of code.
我想把我所有的功能都放在我的代码屏幕上
Cuz I'd like to have all of my functions
be visible on my code screen at once,
在我的编辑里
in my editor at once.
但每过一段时间也许比我承认的要多
But every once in a while,
maybe more often than I'd like to admit,
我的功能是 100 行还是 200 行就行了
my functions are 100 lines or
200 lines long, it does happen.
你们中的一些可能有一些长的功能，好的。
Some of you probably have
some long functions, okay.
如果我在函数中声明某个函数变量和
If I declare on line one of
a function some variable and
是叫老师的，我是用它来的，我用的
it's called teacher and I'm using it for
some purpose, and I use it for
几行然后我们就会有 200 条线然后我又要用这个变量了
a few lines and then we go down 200 lines
and then I need to use the variable again.
如果我开始进入并分配给它
If I just start accessing it and
assigning to it, and
读者在那里一直滚动着，看到老师，
the reader is scrolled all the way
down there and they see that teacher,
对他们的影响是不清楚的。
it is not gonna be clear to
them what scope it comes from.
他们要怎么解决这个问题
How are they gonna solve that?
他们得把 200 条线卷起来然后去找个 var 老师
They're gonna have to scroll 200 lines
up and go look for a var teacher.
>> Kyle Simpson: 我想做的是在任何地方重复使用变量
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: What I like to do is any
place where I'm going to reuse a variable
在一个很明显已经被宣布的地方
in a place where it's not obviously
already having been declared,
我要重新声明要清楚
is I redeclare it to make it clear and
完全明白它属于什么范围。
completely unambiguous
what scope it belongs to.
所以我把另一个变量标识在 200 线上
So I put another var id down on
line 200 to show you that I'm
在此作用域中使用称为 " 标识 " 的变量，
using a variable called id in this scope,
无论其是否仅声明一次或重新声明。
regardless of whether it was declared
only once or being redeclared.
无法在作用域内复用 Var 。
Vars can be reused within a scope,
lets cannot.
所以有语义上的原因和行为上的原因
So there are both semantic reasons and
behavioral reasons why I think var and
应该在您的程序中共存，而不是让它成为另一个。
let should coexist in your program
rather than having one be the other.
事实上我想说基本上所有电脑都没时间
As a matter of fact, I would say,
essentially no time in all of computer
科学历史曾经是真实的 X 是新的
science history has that ever really
been true, that x is the new y.
那不是件事
That's just not a thing.
我们创造了新的东西，但它几乎没有，在所有东西的范围内
We create new stuff, but it almost never,
in the whole scope of everything that
我们发明了一个新事物的案例
we've invented, it is almost never
the case that when you create a new thing
完全彻底地排除了之前的事
it completely and totally obviates
the previous thing immediately.
几乎都是它的预兆
It's almost always that it augments.
所以我们这里就是一个例子
And so
what we have here is an example where
我们喜欢写有新 var 的博客帖子
we love to write blog post that
say let is the new var and
我们喜欢有 T 恤衫说我们喜欢做全球发现
we love to have t-shirts that say that and
we love to do global find and
替换，但实际上不是新 var，它是加 var。
replaces, but in reality let is not
the new var, it is let plus var.
它们都对我们的计划有用。
They both are useful for our programs.
你有问题吗
You had a question?
>> 演讲者 1: 是的，如果你愿意的话，如果你有两次 id 的话。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: Yeah, if you,
like in this case, if you have id twice.
是存储在同一内存位置的 var ，或者
Is then the var stored in
the same memory location or
是否有两个相互引用的内存位置，或者?
are there two memory locations
that reference each other or?
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 只有一个大理石。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Just one marble.
请记住我们之前的示例，当我们在第 6 行上运行第二个 var 时
Remember from our earlier example, when
we run across the second var on line six
在编译阶段，我们会说，哎蓝色的范围，
during the compilation phase,
we would have said, hey blue scope,
哎查找记录的范围，有没有听说过这个叫 id的东西 ?
hey scope of lookup record,
ever heard of this thing called id?
他会说，是的，他会说，
And he would have said, yep,
and he would have said,
好的冷静点没事的
okay cool, nothing to do, no op.
已经有一个叫做 id的大理石
There's already a marble called id.